<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rdf:RDF xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#"
         xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">
   <rdf:Description>
      <dc:title>The Discovery and Conquest of the Molucco and Philippine Islands</dc:title>
      <dc:creator>Bartolomé Juan Leonardo de Argensola (1562–1631)</dc:creator>
      <dc:creator>John Stevens (d. 1726)</dc:creator>
      <dc:publisher>Project Gutenberg, Urbana, Illinois, USA., 2013-08-12</dc:publisher>
      <dc:date>2013-08-12</dc:date>
      <dc:rights>This eBook is for the use of anyone anywhere at no cost and with almost no restrictions whatsoever. You may copy it, give it away or re-use it under the terms of the Project Gutenberg License included with this eBook or online at www.gutenberg.org.
This eBook is produced by the Online Distributed Proofreading Team at www.pgdp.net.
Scans for this book can be found on-line in the Internet Archive (copy 1, 2). The same scans are also available from the University of Michigan Library (copy 1).
A different scan set is available from the Bodleian Library (copy 1). These scans include a dedication not present in the University of Michigan copy, but lack most of the plates.
The Spanish original, Conquista de las Islas Malucas al rey Felipe III, was published in 1609, and is also available on-line as scans (copy 1, 2, 3; in an 1891 reprint: 1, 2, 3).
The illustrations in this edition are of low quality and damaged, but the best available. If you have access to better quality scans of the illustrations, please provide these to Project Gutenberg for inclusion in this edition.
</dc:rights>
      <dc:subject>Maluku (Indonesia) -- History</dc:subject>
      <dc:subject>Philippines -- History</dc:subject>
      <dc:description>A histroy of the conquest and early colonisation of the Philippines. This translation is one of the first books on the Philippines written in English.</dc:description>
      <dc:identifier>pg:43451</dc:identifier>
   </rdf:Description>
</rdf:RDF>